

CONTACT

+254702463477

✓ vincentmunywoki12@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vincentmunywoki-523a21252/

https://github.com/vincentMunywoki? tab=repositories

EDUCATION

Aug 2024 - Todate

POWER LEARN PROJECT ORG

• Software development

Sep 2020 - Graduating on 19th Sep 2024

UNIVERSITY OF EMBU

- Bachelor of Science In Information Technology
- Second class honors upper division

Jan 2016 - Nov 2019

THATHA HIGH SCHOOL

- Kenya certificate of secondary education
- Grade C+

Jan 2006 - Nov 2015

KANYONGA PRIMARY SCHOOL

- Kenya certificate of Primary education
- Marks 296/500

VINCENT MUNYWOKI

IT ASSOCIATE AND WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic IT Associate with a strong foundation in programming languages (C#, VB.NET, ReactJS), web development (HTML, CSS, JS), database management (MySQL), and UI/UX design. I possess excellent communication, critical thinking, teamwork, and problem-solving skills.

Currently, I'm actively upskilling in Angular at Power Learners Project Organization, further solidifying my front-end development expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Havalaa Technologies LTD

Product Designer - Contract

JULY 2024 - AUG 2024

- Designing intuitive and minimalist UI that communicates a clear message or function per page.
- Developing wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity designs using Figma, ensuring simplicity and user engagement.
- Working with the development team to ensure design fidelity in the final product.
- Continuously refining designs to enhance user experience and interface aesthetics.
- Conducting User research



Jomo Kenyatta University Of Agriculture and Technology

ICT Support - Attachee

MAY 2023 - AUG 2023

- Managed and maintained the university's network infrastructure, including hardware and software systems, specializing in VOIP configuration and switch management.
- Provided technical support and training to faculty, staff, and students. Resolved network and software issues through various support channels.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Responsive Web Design Essentials - HTML5 CSS3 Bootstrap
- Figma UI UX Design Essentials
- Overview of IoT Technologies
- Overview of Artificial Intelligence
- Artificial Intelligence fundamentals
- Development and Basic
 Concepts of Cloud Computing
- Cloud Advanced: Architecture and Technologies
- · Huawei certified ICT associate

SKILLS

- Project Management
- C# and VB.NET
- Angular
- Reactjs
- HTML, CSS and JS
- Database skills (mySQL)
- UI/UX Skills
- Networking skills
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Teamwork and Colaboration
- · Problem-solving skills

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Swahili

MY PROJECTS

1. SMART PARKING STSTEM

 Using the IoT based parking system I made it easy for drivers to access the parking slot available over the internet. This system completely automated the car parking procedure from entry to the exit. I used Adafruit cloud platform to store and process parking data

2. ELECTRONIC LEARNING WEBSITE

• I designed an E-learning platform focusing on integrating set of services that enhances education. The site will help users to select the right platform for their training.

3. E-COMMERCE ADMIN DASHBOARD

 I developed a Responsive Admin Dashboard For an Ecommerce Website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. The dashboard has dark and light options

4. GYM - WEBSITE

• This is a front end gym site, that offers features like session bookings, Training booking and tips for body fitness.

5. QUIZ APPLICATION USING JS

 I developed a quiz application using javaScript only, you can select the level of difficulty for your quiz and also you can set your favorable time per question and also you can select any category you like (e.g politics, Mathematics etc)

6. MY PORTFOLIO

 Currently, I am developing my portfolio using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. I am using frameworks like bootsrap, reactjs and Tailwind.

REFEREES

Dr. Faith Mueni

Lecturer - University of Embu

Phone: 0737766052

Email: mueni.faith@embuni.ac.ke

Dr. Consolanta Gakii

Exam Coordinator - University Of Embu

Phone: 0715319763

Email: gakii.consolata@embuni.ac.ke